## **Dmitrii** Lisin

## Software Programmer, Embedded Programmer

0052, Yerevan, Yerevan AM

☑ mrlisdim@gmail.com ☐ +37441452368





I began my career as an intern at an electronics design firm, I discovered that I enjoyed creating something that worked in real life rather than just inside my computer. I have finished a lot of embedded projects from different spheres and dealt with numerous instruments, protocols, and peripherals. It has always been my intention to write only high-quality, human-readable code. Had prior team leadership experience, but preferred to work as an equal member of the team. In my free time, I also prefer to extend my knowledge of programming languages, techniques, and trends by working with hobby projects.

Python Development	C++ Development	Embedded Development	CI/CD	
Advanced	master	Master	Intermediate	
FastAPI Pydantic ORM	CMake Make STL	C/C++ Zephyr FreeRTOS	Docker Docker Compose	
WAMP protocol Async	Concepts C++17 C++20	STM32 Nordic	Github Actions Gitlab Pipelines	
Threading		Real-time protocols		
		Industrial protocols		
		Stack only programming		
Web Development	Databases	Rust	Common	
Intermediate	Intermediate	Beginner	Git Gitlab Github Reviewing	
HTML CSS JavaScript	PostgreSQL SQLAlchemy	Tauri	Linux Reading schematics	
Typescript React Parcel	PonyORM SQL		Datasheet exploring	
Rollup				
WORK EXPERIENCE (3)				
Software engineer at BostonGe				2022 - Current
Support and enhance a complex  Team leader at LLC "Third Pin"	Python backend that provides an er	nvironment for bioinformatics pipelines t	o calculate.	
	em for embedded electronics based	on distributed micro-services connected	d by PubSub/RPC Web-protocol.	2020 - 2022
<ul> <li>Robster: flexible testing syste</li> </ul>	m for electronic devices (Pvthon, WA	AMP, Microservice, Docker, PostgreSQL	.)	
<ul> <li>Gate valve controller (ARM, S</li> </ul>		,	· /	
•	al training (ARM, Nordic, GPS, UBlox	, Ant)		
Embedded Software Develope	<b>r</b> at LLC "Third Pin"			2013 - 2020
Have been finished more than 2	0 commercial projects in embedded a	area including IoT, safety systems, ship	building.	
<ul> <li>Pastilda: hardware password</li> </ul>	manager (STM32, ARM, Crypto Peri	pheral, SDIO, FatFS, FreeRTOS)		
■ Ship ruder control system (AF	RM, STM32, USB HID, FreeRTOS)			
■ Fire alarm system (ARM, STM	M32)			
MTUTA: Telemetry of vending	machines (ARM, FreeRTOS, USB,	SD, SIMCom, GSM, Ethernet, FTP)		
PROJECTS (2)				
Pastilda	to a m/mantil da			2016 - 2017
https://bitbucket.org/thirdpin_ C++ Embedded Open-source				
		and accura way		
Just Run My Debugger!	d to manage our credentials in handy	and secure way.		2021 - Current
https://github.com/ila-embsys	/justrunmydebugger			2021 04110110
Rust Rescript Tauri React				
Pet project, simple GUI for Open	OCD debugger.			
EDUCATION (2)				
Master Intelligent Technologie	s in Robotics at ITMO University			
Deck alon lotallinent Technolog	des in Bahadias at ITMO Haireasite.			2016 - 2018
Dachelor Intelligent Technolog	gies in Robotics at ITMO University			2012 - 2016
LANGUAGES				
English	Russian			
Fluent	Native Speaker			
INTERESTS —	Basks	Torontino a	hh. an ar well	
Games	Books	_	obby programming	
		Ty	pescript Rust Rescript	